Three AM the cursor blinks alone
새벽 세 시, 커서만 홀로 깜빡이네.
A thousand functions no one's called
천 개의 함수, 불린 적 한 번도 없네.
The build keeps failing line by line
빌드는 줄줄이 계속 실패해도.
But I keep writing through the wall
난 벽을 뚫고 계속 써 내려가.
Dead code running in the dark
죽은 코드, 어둠 속에 돌아가네.
Every class a buried spark
모든 클래스, 묻힌 불꽃 같아.
No one downloads no one plays
아무도 다운받지 않고, 아무도 플레이 않네.
But the compile light still stays
하지만 컴파일 불빛은 여전히 남아.
Designed the maps drew every sprite
맵을 디자인하고, 스프라이트 하나하나 그렸지.
Scored the music through the night
밤새도록 음악을 만들었어.
The folder grows the version climbs
폴더는 커지고, 버전은 올라가고.
A finished game that no one finds
아무도 찾지 못할 완성된 게임.
Dead code running in the dark
죽은 코드, 어둠 속에 돌아가네.
Every class a buried spark
모든 클래스, 묻힌 불꽃 같아.
No one downloads no one plays
아무도 다운받지 않고, 아무도 플레이 않네.
But the compile light still stays
하지만 컴파일 불빛은 여전히 남아.
Dead code running in the dark
죽은 코드, 어둠 속에 돌아가네.
Every class a buried spark
모든 클래스, 묻힌 불꽃 같아.
No one downloads no one plays
아무도 다운받지 않고, 아무도 플레이 않네.
But the compile light still stays
하지만 컴파일 불빛은 여전히 남아.